{
    "name": "Simple Verbs",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to take"
            ],
            "answer": "To Take",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169810.2417226,
            "question": "PRENDERE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tagliare"
            ],
            "answer": "TAGLIARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169800.4823983,
            "question": "To Cut",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to know"
            ],
            "answer": "To Know (a fact)",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522169837.3936758,
            "question": "SAPERE",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "credere"
            ],
            "answer": "CREDERE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522169817.6026702,
            "question": "To Believe",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to open"
            ],
            "answer": "To Open",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169786.0740826,
            "question": "APRIRE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dire"
            ],
            "answer": "DIRE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169807.6990802,
            "question": "To Say / Tell",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "aspettare"
            ],
            "answer": "ASPETTARE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522169834.1939392,
            "question": "To Wait",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cenare"
            ],
            "answer": "CENARE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522169774.4899826,
            "question": "To Dine",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to follow"
            ],
            "answer": "To Follow",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522169934.9776192,
            "question": "SEGUIRE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to drink"
            ],
            "answer": "To Drink",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169899.849635,
            "question": "BERE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to remember"
            ],
            "answer": "To Remember",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169897.2013848,
            "question": "RICORDARE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to understand"
            ],
            "answer": "To Understand",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522169857.56219,
            "question": "CAPIRE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to pass / spend"
            ],
            "answer": "To Pass / Spend",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522169906.5851722,
            "question": "PASSARE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be able to",
                "to be able to do"
            ],
            "answer": "To Be Able To",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522169940.033222,
            "question": "POTERE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to carry / bring / wear"
            ],
            "answer": "To Carry / Bring / Wear",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522169952.3612645,
            "question": "PORTARE",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to read"
            ],
            "answer": "To Read",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522169867.2813466,
            "question": "LEGGERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "stare"
            ],
            "answer": "STARE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170207.1838448,
            "question": "To Stay (to be located / in the state of)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to leave"
            ],
            "answer": "To Leave",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170209.5115373,
            "question": "LASCIARE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to want / desire",
                "to want"
            ],
            "answer": "To Want",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170145.656054,
            "question": "VOLERE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to wish / desire"
            ],
            "answer": "To Wish / Desire",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522170219.1351345,
            "question": "DESIDERARE",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to believe"
            ],
            "answer": "To Believe",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522169970.2248108,
            "question": "CREDERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to dine"
            ],
            "answer": "To Dine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170049.5445137,
            "question": "CENARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "volere"
            ],
            "answer": "VOLERE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522170221.2637084,
            "question": "To Want",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to write"
            ],
            "answer": "To Write",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170079.952467,
            "question": "SCRIVERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "essere"
            ],
            "answer": "ESSERE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170263.6072512,
            "question": "To Be",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "arrivare"
            ],
            "answer": "ARRIVARE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170321.2149398,
            "question": "To Arrive",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to watch"
            ],
            "answer": "To Watch / Look",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170255.3274024,
            "question": "GUARDARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to keep / hold"
            ],
            "answer": "To Keep / Hold",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522170334.134402,
            "question": "TENERE",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "avere"
            ],
            "answer": "AVERE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170323.6388774,
            "question": "To Have",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capire"
            ],
            "answer": "CAPIRE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170275.76721,
            "question": "To Understand",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "finire"
            ],
            "answer": "FINIRE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170286.0627155,
            "question": "To Finish",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to see"
            ],
            "answer": "To See",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170259.3754246,
            "question": "VEDERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to work"
            ],
            "answer": "To Work",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170382.9662092,
            "question": "LAVORARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "conoscere"
            ],
            "answer": "CONOSCERE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170543.196739,
            "question": "To Know / Meet *regular conjugations with some exceptions",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to stay (to be located | to be in a state of)",
                "to stay (be located / in state of)"
            ],
            "answer": "To Stay (to be located / in the state of)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170568.7563753,
            "question": "STARE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to remain",
                "to remain / stay"
            ],
            "answer": "To Remain / Stay",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522170654.6282237,
            "question": "RIMANERE",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sentire"
            ],
            "answer": "SENTIRE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170610.6047018,
            "question": "To Hear / Sense",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mangiare"
            ],
            "answer": "MANGIARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170483.5013318,
            "question": "To Eat",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "must do",
                "to have to (must)"
            ],
            "answer": "To Have To (Must)",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522170661.3724642,
            "question": "DOVERE",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to hear / sense"
            ],
            "answer": "To Hear / Sense",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170479.365661,
            "question": "SENTIRE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to use"
            ],
            "answer": "To Use",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1522170816.2434857,
            "question": "USARE",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to have"
            ],
            "answer": "To Have",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170665.7401447,
            "question": "AVERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "passare"
            ],
            "answer": "PASSARE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170684.1320477,
            "question": "To Pass / Spend",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to finish"
            ],
            "answer": "To Finish",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170678.484312,
            "question": "FINIRE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sequire"
            ],
            "answer": "SEGUIRE",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522170806.8669276,
            "question": "To Follow",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "parlare"
            ],
            "answer": "PARLARE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170767.0595455,
            "question": "To Speak",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "trovare"
            ],
            "answer": "TROVARE",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522170802.6116538,
            "question": "To Find",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to decide"
            ],
            "answer": "To Decide",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522170810.0110118,
            "question": "DECIDERE",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "comprare"
            ],
            "answer": "COMPRARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170898.9062903,
            "question": "To Buy",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "aprire"
            ],
            "answer": "APRIRE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170849.1705587,
            "question": "To Open",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to ask"
            ],
            "answer": "To Ask",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170853.4348562,
            "question": "CHIEDERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to enter"
            ],
            "answer": "To Enter",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522170842.483099,
            "question": "ENTRARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to make / do"
            ],
            "answer": "To Make / Do",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170887.570713,
            "question": "FARE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bollire"
            ],
            "answer": "BOLLIRE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170882.3943508,
            "question": "To Boil",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to put"
            ],
            "answer": "To Put",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522170932.0980723,
            "question": "METTERE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to wait"
            ],
            "answer": "To Wait",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522170958.4498,
            "question": "ASPETTARE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to become"
            ],
            "answer": "To Become",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522171198.4400115,
            "question": "DIVENTARE",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to buy"
            ],
            "answer": "To Buy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171010.92153,
            "question": "COMPRARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiamare"
            ],
            "answer": "CHIAMARE",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522171220.4082296,
            "question": "To Call",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "venire"
            ],
            "answer": "VENIRE",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522171215.151828,
            "question": "To Come",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "portare"
            ],
            "answer": "PORTARE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522171165.736953,
            "question": "To Carry / Bring / Wear",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to eat"
            ],
            "answer": "To Eat",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171036.8976789,
            "question": "MANGIARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vivere"
            ],
            "answer": "VIVERE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171064.2574446,
            "question": "To Live",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "potere"
            ],
            "answer": "POTERE",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522171205.0087163,
            "question": "To Be Able To",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mettere"
            ],
            "answer": "METTERE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171336.135392,
            "question": "To Put",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ricordare"
            ],
            "answer": "RICORDARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171349.7837148,
            "question": "To Remember",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pensare"
            ],
            "answer": "PENSARE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522171355.455253,
            "question": "To Think",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "guardare"
            ],
            "answer": "GUARDARE",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522171372.247522,
            "question": "To Watch / Look",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to cut"
            ],
            "answer": "To Cut",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171228.8799157,
            "question": "TAGLIARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cucinare"
            ],
            "answer": "CUCINARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171299.9356868,
            "question": "To Cook",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to leave"
            ],
            "answer": "To Leave",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522171365.3268895,
            "question": "USCIRE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fare"
            ],
            "answer": "FARE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171253.9041646,
            "question": "To Make / Do",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to come"
            ],
            "answer": "To Come",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522171635.0048187,
            "question": "VENIRE",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to find"
            ],
            "answer": "To Find",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171503.3258984,
            "question": "TROVARE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "usare"
            ],
            "answer": "USARE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171472.6863365,
            "question": "To Use",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "desiderare"
            ],
            "answer": "DESIDERARE",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522171643.8849974,
            "question": "To Wish / Desire",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lasciare"
            ],
            "answer": "LASCIARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171475.7986794,
            "question": "To Leave",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dare"
            ],
            "answer": "DARE",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1522171649.8050687,
            "question": "To Give",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "morire"
            ],
            "answer": "MORIRE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522171560.5898852,
            "question": "To Die",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "entrare"
            ],
            "answer": "ENTRARE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522171603.661203,
            "question": "To Enter",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to die"
            ],
            "answer": "To Die",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171720.6689608,
            "question": "MORIRE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to boil"
            ],
            "answer": "To Boil",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171742.5724485,
            "question": "BOLLIRE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to say / tell"
            ],
            "answer": "To Say / Tell",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1522171847.2920022,
            "question": "DIRE",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tenere"
            ],
            "answer": "TENERE",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1522171838.7478535,
            "question": "To Keep / Hold",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to cook"
            ],
            "answer": "To Cook",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171695.2927232,
            "question": "CUCINARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "amare"
            ],
            "answer": "AMARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171744.4609623,
            "question": "To Love",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to speak"
            ],
            "answer": "To Speak",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171690.0370853,
            "question": "PARLARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lavorare"
            ],
            "answer": "LAVORARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171733.0603304,
            "question": "To Work",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to call"
            ],
            "answer": "To Call",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522172015.9702597,
            "question": "CHIAMARE",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to lunch"
            ],
            "answer": "To Lunch",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522172013.8100355,
            "question": "PRANZARE",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "decidere"
            ],
            "answer": "DECIDERE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522172004.4189181,
            "question": "To Decide",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to know",
                "To Know"
            ],
            "answer": "To Know / Meet *regular conjugations with some exceptions",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522171944.8586226,
            "question": "CONOSCERE",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "diventare"
            ],
            "answer": "DIVENTARE",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522172028.2984414,
            "question": "To Become",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to go"
            ],
            "answer": "To Go",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171895.6277149,
            "question": "ANDARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be"
            ],
            "answer": "To Be",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171852.3711965,
            "question": "ESSERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to arrive"
            ],
            "answer": "To Arrive",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522171920.7475474,
            "question": "ARRIVARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to give"
            ],
            "answer": "To Give",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522172122.497497,
            "question": "DARE",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to love"
            ],
            "answer": "To Love",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522172060.122553,
            "question": "AMARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scrivere"
            ],
            "answer": "SCRIVERE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522172056.146213,
            "question": "To Write",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bere"
            ],
            "answer": "BERE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522172106.5381129,
            "question": "To Drink",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to live"
            ],
            "answer": "To Live",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522172040.3541613,
            "question": "VIVERE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to think"
            ],
            "answer": "To Think",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522172045.6984415,
            "question": "PENSARE",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "andare"
            ],
            "answer": "ANDARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522172108.5072594,
            "question": "To Go",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendere"
            ],
            "answer": "PRENDERE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522172125.5535638,
            "question": "To Take",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sapere"
            ],
            "answer": "SAPERE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522172274.6324475,
            "question": "To Know (a fact)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dovere"
            ],
            "answer": "DOVERE",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1522172289.8569734,
            "question": "To Have To (Must)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiedere"
            ],
            "answer": "CHIEDERE",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1522172277.8169549,
            "question": "To Ask",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "uscire"
            ],
            "answer": "USCIRE",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1522172310.6242416,
            "question": "To Leave",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "leggere"
            ],
            "answer": "LEGGERE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522172217.1370556,
            "question": "To Read",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vedere"
            ],
            "answer": "VEDERE",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1522172183.6012843,
            "question": "To See",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "rimanere"
            ],
            "answer": "RIMANERE",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1522172321.8168948,
            "question": "To Remain / Stay",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pranzare"
            ],
            "answer": "PRANZARE",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1522172231.2013507,
            "question": "To Lunch",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}